{"status":"Success","data":{"question_paper":[{"question_no":"1","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d35\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15 ","option2":"\u0d05\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"2","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 2017 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d1c\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d07\u0d33\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"3","question":"\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d21\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"4","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c ?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d36\u0d36\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"5","question":"\u0d35\u0d7a \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7a \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","option1":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f ","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28","option3":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"6","question":"'\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d38\u0d4d' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d30\u0d18\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d7b","option3":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d05\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"7","question":"2017 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 17-\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 ","option2":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d28\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d26 ","option4":"\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"8","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?","option1":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d7c ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"9","question":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d57\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f ?","option1":"\u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d2f","option2":"\u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d7b 100","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"10","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f","option3":"\r\n\r\n\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4b\u0d7c \r\n","option4":"\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"11","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d0e\u0d7b\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b ?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d27 ","option2":"\u0d32\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d17 ","option4":"\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"12","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d 2017 \u0d06\u0d18\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d1a\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"13","question":"\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 ","option2":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"14","question":"\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d27 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d-400 \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d02\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28 ","option2":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f ","option3":"\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d ","option4":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"15","question":"2018\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d40\u0d28 ","option2":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f ","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"16","question":"\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d32\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d32\u0d02","option2":"\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3e \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 \u0d36\u0d7c\u0d2e","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"17","question":"2018\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?","option1":"\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34 ","option2":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d7c ","option4":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d7c","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"18","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d25\u0d2e \u0d12 \u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d1c\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e ","option3":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d30\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"19","question":"\u0d12\u0d0e\u0d7b\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d28 ?","option1":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d33\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d13\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d41\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"20","question":"\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d02\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f ?","option1":"\u0d36\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d2f ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d48\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30","option4":"\u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"21","question":"'\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15 ' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d02","option4":"\u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"22","question":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7b ?","option1":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d24\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d06\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"23","question":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33","option4":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d33\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"24","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23 \u0d27\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","option1":"1901","option2":"1903","option3":"1905","option4":"1914","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"25","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41 ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d30\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d31","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"26","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4a\u0d38\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7d ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"27","question":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d25 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d0e \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d07 \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"28","question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d35\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 ","option4":"\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"29","question":"\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d7c \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d39\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d21\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d4a\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"30","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d1c \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d06\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d7a","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"31","question":"\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 ","option2":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7a ","option3":"\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"32","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d32\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d24\u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d07-\u0d39\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d2f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"33","question":"23 1\/2 \u0d35\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 ","option2":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 ","option3":"\u0d06\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 ","option4":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d30\u0d47\u0d16","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"34","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d30 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30 ?","option1":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c ","option4":"\u0d06\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"35","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0a\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d24\u0d46\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d39\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"36","question":"\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 21 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d 18 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d47\u0d26\u0d17\u0d24\u0d3f ?","option1":"42","option2":"44","option3":"52","option4":"61","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"37","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d ","option4":"\u0d0e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"38","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d32\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"39","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d36\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d30 ","option2":"\u0d05\u0d27\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d30 ","option3":"\u0d0a\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d30 ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d30 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"40","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b ","option2":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d7b ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"41","question":"\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d26\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d30\u0d15\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28","option3":"\u0d05\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d","option4":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d36\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"42","question":"\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d7c ","option4":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"43","question":"'Why I am an Athiest '\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d2d\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7b ","option3":" \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7e \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d05\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"44","question":"'\u0d17\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47 \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f ' \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f mumbai","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48 ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"45","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d1c\u0d32 \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"46","question":"' \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ?","option1":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34 ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34 ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"47","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d36\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0a\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15 \u0d18\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d1c\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"48","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d7d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28 ","option4":"\u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7e","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"49","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d38\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d06\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"50","question":"\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","option1":"1991","option2":"1994","option3":"1996","option4":"1998","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"51","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d30 ","option3":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d7c ","option4":"\u0d07\u0d33\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"52","question":"\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d2d\u0d43\u0d24\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d32\u0d36\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"53","question":"\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d30 ","option2":"\u0d05\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d40\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30 ","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d21\u0d3e \u0d27\u0d30\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d20\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"54","question":"\u0d36\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d32 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d47\u0d36\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42 \u0d39\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b ?","option1":"\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d4a\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d42\u0d21","option3":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ","option4":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7a \u0d28\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"55","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d2d\u0d17\u0d35\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24 ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"56","question":"\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d7d ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"57","question":"\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d09\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d09\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d09\u0d37\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c \u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"58","question":"\u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32 ","option3":"\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30 ","option4":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"59","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d21 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d7d ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d3f ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"60","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d2d\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d7c ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d7c ","option4":"\u0d27\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"61","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d2d\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d7c ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d7c ","option4":"\u0d27\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7c","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"62","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d15\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d30\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"63","question":"\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d21\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d24\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d2d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"64","question":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"65","question":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7c ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34 ","option4":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"66","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d40\u0d1a\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d10\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d43\u0d17\u0d02","option4":"\u0d15\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"67","question":"\u0d05\u0d02\u0d36\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"68","question":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d 12 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d35\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 ","option3":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"69","question":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","option1":"19","option2":"21","option3":"11","option4":"9","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"70","question":"\u0d38\u0d57\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38 ","option2":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30 ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d7c ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"71","question":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d57\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b ","option4":"\u0d26\u0d41\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"72","question":"\u0d2d\u0d35 \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d28\u0d46 ?","option1":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21","option2":"\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21 ","option3":"\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21 ","option4":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"73","question":"\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d27\u0d42\u0d24\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d7d ","option3":"\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d26\u0d47\u0d39\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d7b","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"74","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7b '\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f' . \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d02","option2":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d02","option3":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d02","option4":"\u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d02 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"75","question":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d41 ","option2":"\u0d27\u0d43\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d41\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d39\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d7b ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"76","question":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d2a\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7e","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d7e","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"77","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e \u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","option1":"\u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"78","question":"\u0d24\u0d32 \u0d24\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d48\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d36\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15 ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15","option4":"\u0d09\u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"79","question":"He gaveup that Idea . \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37 ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d06 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41","option2":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d06 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d06 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41","option4":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d06 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"80","question":"\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d05\u0d24\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"81","question":"The Synonym of 'Candid'","option1":"Dull","option2":"Frank","option3":"Deep","option4":"Free","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"82","question":"His house has four ..... choose the right word .","option1":"stories","option2":"story","option3":"storeys","option4":"storey","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"83","question":"An assembly of hearers. Choose the right One word.","option1":"Audience","option2":"Mob","option3":"crowd","option4":"Congregation","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"84","question":"Father asked me why I told a lie. Choose the direct Speech .","option1":"Father said to me, \"Why did you told a lie ?\"","option2":"Father said to me , \"Why you tell a lie ?\"","option3":"Father told me , \"Why do you tell a lie ?\"","option4":"Father said to me , \"Why did you tell a lie ?\"","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"85","question":"She acted ...... she was mad. Use the right Conjunction.","option1":"althogh","option2":"as though","option3":"as well as","option4":"because","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"86","question":"His handwriting is .... than mine ","option1":"best","option2":"more better","option3":"better","option4":"good","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"87","question":"Women can't .... a secret. Use the correct Phrasal Verb.","option1":"keep back","option2":"keep away","option3":"keep on","option4":"keep down","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"88","question":"Choose the wrongly spelt word.","option1":"Address","option2":"Distress","option3":"Reddress","option4":"Harass","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"89","question":"The news ... shocking . Choose the right Verb.","option1":"is","option2":"are","option3":"were","option4":"have","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"90","question":"I will talk to you in .... minutes.","option1":"few","option2":"a little","option3":"the few","option4":"a few","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"91","question":"20 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d 0.05 ?","option1":"0.5","option2":"0.1","option3":"0.25","option4":"0.025","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"92","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d46\u0d7a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d36\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 5 : 4 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d.\u0d06\u0d15\u0d46 3600 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d7a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","option1":"2000","option2":"1600","option3":"1800","option4":"2200","answer":"0"},{"question_no":"93","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 35% , 140 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","option1":"400","option2":"420","option3":"350","option4":"1400","answer":"0"}]},"code":"100"}